# **Janice Libby Thomas**

DATA ANALYST

#### **Profile**

Seasoned Seasoned software professional with about 2.3 years of experience in Capital Market domain as QA.

Recognized as Software Tester with good knowledge in SQL and Selenium, Core Java.

Certified in IIT-M Advance Programming Profession & Master Data Science Program.

Also Have good knowledge in Analyzing Data, Cleaning and Visualizing the data using Python.

## **Employment History**

#### TEST ANALYST, BNP PARIBAS INDIA SOLUTIONS, Chennai

JUNE 2020 - AUGUST 2022

Understanding Business requirement and Functional

Specifications.

Involved in Test Planning, Test case Creation and Test Data

Creation, Performing Test Execution, Reporting Defects and Defect

Tracking till closure in the test management tool ALM.

Performing Smoke Testing, Regression testing, Integration

testing and User Acceptance Testing.

Handling the Project work streams on my own and discussing

the scenarios with business directly.

Maintaining and adding new test cases in selenium.

## Internships

#### INTERN TRAINEE, BNP PARIBAS, CHENNAI

JANUARY 2020 - MAY 2020

Utilized knowledge of Java to create automation test scripts

in selenium.

#### Education

IIT-M Advanced Programming Professional & Master Data Science, GUVI, Chennai

OCTOBER 2022 - FEBRUARY 2023

BACHELOR OF ENGNEERING IN COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEERING, VELTECH HIGHTECH DR RANGARAJAN DR SAKUNTHALA ENGINEERING COLLEGE, CHENNAI

AUGUST 2016 - MAY 2020

#### **Details**

Bangalore

India

9443922581

abrahamjanice7@gmail.com

#### Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

#### Skills

Python ( Numpy, Pandas, Scikit-Learn, Matplotlib, Seaborn, Plotly)

SQL

MongoDB

Snscrape

Streamlit

Core Java

Git

#### Languages

English

Tamil

### **PROJECTS**

#### **Email Registration:**

Creating new mail account, Updating the password using python.

Skill Used: Python- Click

#### **Telephone Directory:**

Creating and Updating a Telephone directory using python and SQL as database.

Skill Used: Python, SQL - Click

#### **Aadhar Card Directory:**

Creating new aadhar card for user, Updating the existing details of created user using aadhar no, Validating the mail by OTP, Allowing user to Download PDF of aadhar card.

Skill used: Python, MongoDB - Click

#### **Twiiter Scraping:**

Scrapping the data from Twitter using Snscrape. Created GUI using Stramlit, which allows user to search

list of tweets by username or hashtags, on clicking update button user can updload the data searched into MongoDB, allows user to download details in CSV and JSON Format.

Skill Used: Python(Snscrape, Pandas), Mongo DB, Streamlit. - Click

#### **Zomato Dataset EDA:**

Analysing Zomato Dataset and to build a Plotly Dashboard.

Skill Used: Python( Pandas, Plotly) - Click

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### **BRAVO AWARD**

Handled various subjects that were core, crucial and critical successfully in short time.